<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Shriman</title>
    <link href="https://shrimansoft.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://shrimansoft.github.io" />
    <updated>2022-11-16T01:59:22+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Shriman Keshri</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://shrimansoft.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>A different story!! </title>
        <author>
            <name>Shriman Keshri</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shrimansoft.github.io/a-different-story.html"/>
        <id>https://shrimansoft.github.io/a-different-story.html</id>

        <updated>2022-11-16T01:59:22+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Things we see will change if we tell ourselves a different story. We usually tell the story to ourselves, which makes us feel special; in the story in which everyone loves us, I am the one, To whom everyone should care about. We have justification&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <blockquote class="blockquote">Things we see will change if we tell ourselves a different story.</blockquote>
<p>We usually tell the story to ourselves, which makes us feel special; in the story in which everyone loves us, I am the one, To whom everyone should care about.</p>
<blockquote class="blockquote">Things we see will change if we tell ourselves a different story. </blockquote>
<p>We have justification for all the moves we have made. Sometimes we create <strong>false assumptions</strong> to justify our desires and the things we have done.</p>
<blockquote class="blockquote">Things we see will change if we tell ourselves a different story. </blockquote>
<p>We made <strong>false assumptions</strong> to justify ourselves so we would be the <strong>good person in our story</strong>. Sometimes these stories are very far from the truth. But when we realize that it makes us break and cross, it puts us on the ground. Thoughts and observations collide with the need to update our beliefs.</p>
<blockquote class="blockquote">Things we see will change if we tell ourselves a different story. </blockquote>
<p>These assumptions we made to justify ourselves. Through this,<strong> we form our personality</strong>. Since we want to be good in that story { we told ourselves}. <strong>We have to behave according to the assumptions we have made</strong>. There are some examples of these assumptions.</p>
<ol>
<li>I love you</li>
<li>I hate you</li>
<li>I am dumb</li>
<li>We are friends</li>
<li>I have a high temper</li>
<li>Yes, but I am like that</li>
<li>I am introvert</li>
<li>I don't go and talk first</li>
</ol>
<p>and many more...</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Things we see will change if we tell ourselves a different story. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>So what do we do?</p>
<p>So what is the story I should tell ourselves?</p>
<p>I don't know the answer, and I don't know that we should tell this story ourselves.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Why should we have to tell a story to ourselves in the first place? </p>
</blockquote>
<p>I want you to think. <strong>Why did we tell stories to ourselves why?</strong> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Deep question</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shriman Keshri</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shrimansoft.github.io/deep-question.html"/>
        <id>https://shrimansoft.github.io/deep-question.html</id>

        <updated>2022-11-15T15:47:13+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    This is the list of questions that makes me carry on. Why do we exist? Do People Have Free Will? Is Nature Moving Towards Dissolution Or Integration? What Gives Life Its Meaning? Why Do We Create Art? Does Time Have A Beginning Or An End?&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This is the list of questions that makes me carry on. </p>
<ol>
<li>
<h4>Why do we exist? </h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">Do People Have Free Will? </h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">Is Nature Moving Towards Dissolution Or Integration?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">What Gives Life Its Meaning?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">Why Do We Create Art?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">Does Time Have A Beginning Or An End?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">Is Our Universe 'Real'?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask"><em>How</em> Do You <em>Explain</em> Consciousness?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">What, Exactly, Makes You… <em>You</em>?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">If The Only Thing I Know Is That I Know Nothing, Do I Know Something?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask"> If I Were Omnipotent, Could I Create A Rock So Heavy I Couldn't Lift It?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">If Every Cell In My Body Gets Replaced Over 7 Years, Will I Still Be Me In 7 Years?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 class="quest questions-to-ask">If No One Observes An Event, Did It Happen?</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4>Why is there something rather than nothing? </h4>
</li>
</ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
